Jorge Martinez

11900 Kathyann St, Lakeview Terrace, CA 91342 Cell: (818) 741-8370 jorge.martinez.530@my.csun.edu

Summary

Experienced tutor with diverse subject expertise. Very friendly and enthusiastic professional with Associate's Degree in Mathematics and advanced knowledge in mathematics, engineering, and computer science. Adept at improving both group and individual concept understanding and performance.

Education

B.S. in Computer Science & Mathematics In Progress

California State University, Northridge (3.786 GPA)

Northridge, CA

- Dean's List

A.A. in Mathematics Spring 2017

Los Angeles Mission College Sylmar, CA

- Full Time President's Honor

Work Experience

Los Angeles Mission College Spring 2019 - Present

- Math Tutor

Data Science & Mathematical Modeling Group Summer 2015

- Data Science Intern

M.S. Aerospace Fall 2012 - Spring 2013

- CNC Machinist

Publications

Using Common Academic Indicators to Predict Graduation Rates at CSUN, 2005-2014. With A. Miller, R. Wolff, B. Shapiro, and C. Shubin. 14 pages. March 22, 2019. https://journals.calstate.edu/pump/article/view/225/392

Relevant Coursework

Calculus I | Calculus II | Calculus III | Linear Algebra | Probability | Statistics

Physics I | Physics II | College Algebra | Trigonometry | Geometry

Java | C++ | C | Advanced Data Structures | Scientific Computing

Relevant Skills

Algorithm Design & Analysis

Profficient in LaTex, C/C++, Java, Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, SQL.